luveria.com 2012-09-19

# Luveria - Privacy Policy.

_**Luveria Privacy Notice**_

**Privacy Notice**

April 01, 2009

* * *

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information when you use this site including the information provided when you use this site. 

**Personal information**

* * *

**A.** Luveria asks for some personal information when you create an Account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access.

**B.** As a Luveria member, you can create a profile or a Luveria community that includes personal information, such as your gender, age, occupation, hobbies, and interests, plus other content, such as photos. This information may be accessed and viewed by other Luveria members.

**C.** Unlike other social networking sites, Luveria allows you to control and limit access to certain information that can be viewed by others.

**D.** When you invite new members into your network or send messages through Luveria, we collect and maintain information associated with those messages, including email addresses and content.

**E.** When you send and receive SMS messages to or from the Luveria website, we collect and maintain information associated with those messages, such as the phone number, the wireless carrier associated with the phone number, the content of the message, and the date and time of the transaction.

**Uses**

* * *

**A.** When you send messages through Luveria, your username will be identified in the message. We may also use your username and email address to notify you of new members, messages, or other information as applicable in connection with the services offered at Luveria.

**B.** When you send and receive SMS messages to or from the Luveria, we use the data we collect to operate, develop and improve our services. Our third party providers also may collect data about your SMS usage in order to provide the service. In addition, your wireless carrier may collect data about your SMS usage. Their practices are governed by their own privacy policies.

**Your choices**

* * *

**A.** Unlike other social networking sites, Luveria allows you to control and limit access to certain information that can be viewed by others. You can use the display setting buttons to show or hide certain information such that it could be available to all Luveria members, or to a certain members of your choice or not at all.

**B.** You can update your profile information at any time by clicking on the "edit profile" link when you log on to your account in Luveria.

**C.** Messages you receive from others on Luveria can be sent to your message folders or forwarded to your mobile via SMS, depending on the preferences you choose in the "Mobile Settings" page.

**D.** You can terminate your account at any time. To learn how, click here. If you terminate your account, your profile, including any messages in your inbox, will be removed from the site and deleted from orkut servers. Because of the way we maintain this service such deletion may not be immediate, and residual copies of your profile information may remain on backup media.

**E.** You can opt out of receiving service/promotional emails/sms/wap from Luveria services by either clicking on the link given there or sending an email to [support@luveria.com](mailto:support@Luveria.com)

**More information**

* * *

For more information about our privacy practices or if you have additional questions, please contact us any time. Or write to us at:
